Edward Bleier Papers
Edward Bleier Papers
- Licensing files
  - Wonder Woman (Box 62)
  - Wonder Woman, 1976-1978; correspondence; 2 folders (Box 62)
  - The Wonder Years (Box 62)
  - Woodstock
    - Woodstock, 1989-1990; 2 folders (Box 62)
    - Woodstock, 1989-1990; 8 folders (Box 63)
    - Woodstock, 4 folders (Box 64)
    - Woodstock (movie), 2 folders (Box 64)
  - World According to Garp (Box 64)
  - Wrestling Ernest Hemingway (Box 64)
  - Wrongfully Accused (Box 64)
  - Wyatt Earp (Box 64)
  - The Yakuza Conspiracy (Box 64)
  - Year Without Santa Claus (Box 65)
  - Yellow Rose (Box 65)
  - Yellowstone Kelly (Box 65)
  - Yes, Virgina There Is a Santa Claus (Box 65)
  - Young Bucks (Box 65)
  - Young Einstein (Box 65)
  - Young Men With Unlimited Capital (Box 65)
  - You Can't Take It With You (Box 65)
  - You've Got Mail (Box 65)
  - Zandy's Bride (Box 65)
  - Zelig (Box 65)
  - Zeppelin (Box 65)
  - Zero Effect (Box 65)
- Media
  - Audio
    - Economics of Cable TV seminar (Side 5; Side 6) Paul Kagan, Associates, Inc., New York, NY, 03/15/1984; bleier_e_064; running time 90:00; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 66)
    - Economics of Cable TV seminar (Side 7; Side 8) Paul Kagan, Associates, Inc., New York, NY, 03/15/1984; bleier_e_065; running time 90:00; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 66)
    - Ed Bleier Broadcasting Day Warner Bros. Music; New York, New York, 01/17/1981; bleier_e_066; running time 90:00; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 66)
    - Edward Bleier Reception - Speeches, bleier_e_067; running time 60:00; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 67)
    - Edward Bleier Reception - Speeches, bleier_e_068; running time 22:00; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 67)
    - A New Look at New Revenue Opportunities, Aug 1993; bleier_e_069; CTAM 1993 Annual Meeting Bleier, Burr, Fajersky, Greene, Smith, Thomas; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 66)
    - The New Mass Media Producers Lecture at the New School (Tape 1) The New School; New York, N.Y., 12/09/1982; bleier_e_070; Neil Hickey moderator; Klein, Halmi, Bleier, Geller; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 66)
    - The New Mass Media Producers Lecture at the New School (copy) #2 The New School; New York, N.Y., 12/09/1982; bleier_e_071; Neil Hickey moderator; Klein, Halmi, Bleier, Geller; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 66)
    - USC Lecture: Edward Bleier COMM (1 of 3) Take One Productions; Tustin, CA, 03/23/2005; bleier_e_072; running time 63:00; CD (Box 66)
      See also Video: USC Lecture: Edward Bleier COMM Take One Productions; Tustin, CA for video version.
    - USC Lecture: Edward Bleier COMM (2 of 3) Take One Productions; Tustin, CA, 03/23/2005; bleier_e_073; running time 53:00; CD (Box 66)
    - USC Lecture: Edward Bleier COMM (3 of 3) Take One Productions; Tustin, CA, 03/23/2005; bleier_e_074; running time 45:00; CD (Box 66)
    - Chuck Barris Tribute, Sep 2007; bleier_e_076; DVD (Box 66)
  - Video
    - 20/20, bleier_e_001; running time 60:00; VHS (Box 66)
    - 50 Years of Bugs Bunny in 3 1/2 Minutes, Warner Bros. Animation, Inc., Burbank, CA, 07/25/1991; bleier_e_060; running time 3:30; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic (Box 66)
    - 60 Minutes, bleier_e_002; running time 60:00; VHS (Box 66)
    - 60 Minutes: Don’t Count Them Out, 01/22/1995; bleier_e_003; VHS (Box 67)
    - Americanization of EmilyWarner Bros-Pay TV, 12/07/2000; bleier_e_004; running time 114:53; VHS (Box 67)
    - Angels and Insects: For Your Consideration, bleier_e_005; Best Costume Design: Paul Brown; Samuel Goldwyn Entertainment; VHS (Box 67)
    - Bamboozle (Pilot), 1985; bleier_e_006; VHS (Box 66)
    - Bamboozle (Pilot), bleier_e_062; running time 60:00; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic (Box 67)
    - Bugs Bunny/Looney Tunes All Star 50th..., Warner Bros-Pay TV, 02/10/1996; bleier_e_007; running time 60:00; VHS (Box 66)
    - Bugs Bunny/Looney Tunes All Star 50th..., Warner Bros-Pay TV, 02/10/1996; bleier_e_008; running time 60:00; VHS (Box 66)
    - Children of the Holocaust, bleier_e_009; running time 68:12; VHS (Box 67)
    - Edward Bleier on Martha Stewart Living: Thanksgiving Ceremony, Martha Stewart Living Television, 04/02/2004; bleier_e_010; VHS (Box 66)
    - Everest North Wall: 17 Gave Their Best, bleier_e_061; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic (Box 66)
    - Family Game (Pilot), 2007; bleier_e_011; VHS (Box 66)
    - Gathering of Friends of Palmer Weber (Original), 09/24/1986; bleier_e_012; VHS (Box 66)
    - George Schlatter Productions: Laugh-In 25th Anniversary Special, George Schlatter Productions, 02/03/1993; bleier_e_013; VHS (Box 67)
    - Guild Hall, Steven Spielberg intro, Warner Bros., bleier_e_014; VHS (Box 66)
    - Guild Hall / Bravo 1999, Murray Hill Studios, Inc., New York, NY, 03/26/1999; bleier_e_015; VHS (Box 66)
    - Guild Hall Message Steven Spielberg, Murray Hill Studios, Inc., New York, NY, 11/11/1998; bleier_e_016; running time 2:07; VHS (Box 66)
    - Heaven and Earth (Digital Cut, Part 1 Only), Warner Bros. Video Operations, Burbank, CA, 08/03/1995; bleier_e_017; VHS (Box 66)
    - Heaven & Earth: The Mini-Series, PDR Productions, Inc., New York, NY, 03/11/1994; bleier_e_018; running time 0:60; VHS (Box 66)
    - Heaven & Earth: The Mini Series, Magnetic Image Video Inc., New York, New York, 02/15/1996; bleier_e_019; running time 0:60; VHS (Box 67)
    - Heaven & Earth: The Mini Series, Magnetic Image Video Inc., New York, New York, 02/15/1996; bleier_e_020; running time 0:60; VHS (Box 67)
    - Les Miserables - 1995 Episode 2/3, California Video Center, Los Angeles, CA, 01/18/1996; bleier_e_021; running time 60:00; VHS (Box 67)
    - Les Miserables - 1995 Episode 3/3, California Video Center, Los Angeles, CA, 01/18/1996; bleier_e_022; running time 60:00; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screeners) Episode 1, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/28/1989; bleier_e_023; running time 58:59; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screener) Episode 2, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/28/1989; bleier_e_024; running time 58:56; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screener) Episode 3, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/29/1989; bleier_e_025; running time 59:00; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screener) Episode 4, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/28/1989; bleier_e_026; running time 59:07; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screener) Episode 5, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/28/1989; bleier_e_027; running time 59:08; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screener) Episode 6, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/28/1989; bleier_e_028; running time 59:16; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screener) Episode 7, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/29/1989; bleier_e_029; running time 58:04; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screener) Episode 8, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/17/1989; bleier_e_030; running time 58:51; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screener) Episode 8, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/28/1989; bleier_e_031; running time 58:51; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screener) Episode 9, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/29/1989; bleier_e_032; running time 58:54; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screener) Episode 10, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/30/1989; bleier_e_033; running time 59:11; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screener) Episode 11, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/28/1989; bleier_e_034; running time 59:19; VHS (Box 67)
    - Life on Earth (Screener) Episode 13, Warner Bros. Pay-TV, Hollywood, CA, 08/30/1989; bleier_e_035; running time 57:15; VHS (Box 67)
    - Martin Scorsese Intro to Broadcast of "Goodfellas", PDR Productions, Inc., New York, N.Y., 05/13/1993; bleier_e_036; running time 0:48; VHS (Box 67)
    - Mervyn Leroy Retrospective, Magnetic Image Video Inc., New York, New York, Jun 1994; 03/31/1999;; bleier_e_037; VHS (Box 66)
    - Stanley Kubrick Season Compilation Promo Plus 10" Promos, British Sky Broadcasting Ltd., Isleworth, Middlesex, 08/03/1995; June/July 1995; bleier_e_038; VHS (Box 66)
      Note with item: "Dear Ed: Stanley sent me the attached tapes to forward on to you. BSkyB did a 'Stanley Kubrick Directs' series at 10:00pm on successive weeks highlighting the films noted. Alexander Walker, the London Times chief critic, was the host of the series. Stanley thought you might be interested. Best regards, Richard Fox"; 1 Kubrick Season (30" Compilation Promo); 2 Paths Of Glory (10" Sunday); 3 Paths of Glory (10" Tonight); 4 Dr Strangelove (10" Sunday); 5 Dr Strangelove (10" Tonight); 6 The Shining (10" Sunday); 7 The Shining (10" Tonight); 8 Full Metal Jacket (10" Sunday); 9 Full Metal Jacket (10" Tonight)
    - Stanley Kubrick Season Intro/Outro Sequence, British Sky Broadcasting Ltd; Isleworth, Middlesex, June/July 1995; bleier_e_039; 1 Barry Lyndon; 2 Killer’s Kiss; 3 The Killing; 4 Paths of Glory; 5 Dr Strangelove; 6 The Shining; 7 Making of The Shining; 8 Full Metal Jacket; VHS (Box 66)
    - Steven Spielberg Guild Hall Message, Warner Bros., bleier_e_040; VHS (Box 66)
    - Steven Spielberg Guild Hall Message, Local TV, Inc., Wainscott, NY, bleier_e_041; VHS (Box 66)
    - Ted Kennedy (CBS Reports), bleier_e_042; running time 60:00; VHS (Box 66)
    - The New Dating Game, bleier_e_043; VHS (Box 66)
    - The New Dating Game, bleier_e_063; running time 60:00; 3/4 inch videotape: U-matic (Box 67)
    - The Syracuse Spirit, Syracuse University Video Communications, Syracuse, NY, bleier_e_044; VHS (Box 66)
    - True Romance Demo, bleier_e_045; running time 92:00; VHS (Box 66)
    - TV Forum (PM) 20th, Magnetic Image Video Inc., New York, New York, 11/20/1997; 12/04/1997; bleier_e_046; VHS (Box 67)
    - TV Forum (PM) Episode 1/2, TV UN ONU, 11/20/1997; 12/01/1997; bleier_e_047; VHS (Box 66)
    - TV Forum (PM) Episode 2/2, TV UN ONU, 11/20/1997; 12/01/1997; bleier_e_048; VHS (Box 66)
    - TV Programming Discussion Waldorf Astoria, 02/07/1985; bleier_e_049; VHS (Box 66)
    - UJA-Federation Bob Wright Dinner: Ed Bleier (only), UJA-Federation, New York, N.Y., 03/18/1998; bleier_e_050; VHS (Box 66)
    - UJA-Federation Wright Dinner Video: NBC Video of the Night... UJA-Federation, New York, N.Y., bleier_e_051; VHS (Box 66)
    - USC Lecture: Edward Bleier COMM Take One Productions, Tustin, CA, 03/23/2005; bleier_e_075; running time 160:00; DVD (Box 66)
      See also Audio: USC Lecture: Edward Bleier COMM Take One Productions, Tustin, CA for audio-only version.
    - Warner Bros. "Escape From Hell" Cut Down Version, Magnetic Image Video Inc., New York, New York, 07/15/1998; bleier_e_052; VHS (Box 66)
    - Warner Bros. Ed Bleier - Speeches, video cut down, Warner Bros., bleier_e_053; running time 30:00; VHS (Box 66)
    - Warner Bros. Ed Bleier - Speeches, audio only, bleier_e_054; running time 120:00; VHS (Box 66)
    - Warner Brothers 50th Anniversary of Looney Tunes "Bugs" 31-33 50th Ann., Broadway Video, New York, N.Y., 02/11/1987; bleier_e_055; running time 120:00; VHS (Box 67)
    - Warner Bros. Marketing & Advertising "History of Warner Bros. TV", All Post, Burbank, CA, 05/20/1994; bleier_e_056; running time 5:00; VHS (Box 66)
    - Warner Brothers Television: Comedy Courtroom (Re-Edited Version) (Copy 1), CC Visual, New York, N.Y., bleier_e_057; running time 30:00; VHS (Box 66)
    - Warner Brothers Television: Comedy Courtroom (Re-Edited Version) (Copy 2), CC Visual, New York, N.Y., bleier_e_058; running time 30:00; VHS (Box 66)
    - Water Meditation, bleier_e_059; running time 120:00; VHS (Box 66)
- Memorabilia
  - AMC 10th Anniversary, 2000 (Box 69)
  - AMC snowglobe (Box 68)
  - Apax Partners Fund, 1991 (Box 69)
  - BBC World Service (Box 69)
  - Bear Stearns Media Entertainment Conference participants' plaque, 1989 (Box 68)
  - Cable Advertising Conference (Box 69)
  - Calculator / abacus desk item (Box 68)
  - CarolCo. desk clock (Box 69)
  - CATV Chicago "Thank you" paperweight (Box 68)
  - Cinemax metal paperweight (Box 68)
  - International Summer Consumer Electronics Show, Innovations '87 award for 'Life on Earth', 1987; plaque (Box 68)
  - DIVA Systems Corp. / On-Set Interactive Television souvenir semi truck, 2 pieces, cab and body (Box 68)
  - HBO 10th Anniversary crystal paperweight, 1982 (Box 68)
  - HBO / Cinemax miniature spotlight (Box 68)
  - International TV Council Fellow certificate (Oversize 1)
  - Italia "Radio e TV Record, S. Paulo 25-10-79 Mr & Mrs Edward Bleier" silver skyscraper, 25 Oct 1979 (Box 68)
  - Jerrold's "World of Impulse", wooden stand only, appears to be missing whatever was formerly on the stand (Box 68)
  - NATPE "In appreciation" cameraman sculptures, 1975; 1978; 2 items (Box 68)
  - NCTA "On with the best" crystal pyramid (Box 68)
  - Nickelodeon plastic snowglobe (Box 69)
  - Oppenheimer Financial Conference participants' plaque (Box 68)
  - People's Court brass plaque, 1989 (Box 68)
  - Photograph of Bleier and others, 1998 (Oversize 1)
  - Photographs of Edward Bleier, 8x10 black and white (Oversize 1)
  - Request TV piggy bank (Box 69)
  - Request TV gold slinky in wooden box (Box 68)
  - SBCA Sky Forum marble pencil holder (Box 68)
  - Silver Dictaphone Award, organization unknown; wooden plaque and nameplate only, missing unidentified attachment (Box 68)
  - Syracuse Society of Fellows metal plaque (Box 68)
  - Syracuse University VPA paperweight, 1987 (Box 68)
  - Telemundo globe paperweight (Box 68)
  - UJA Federation of New York "with deepest appreciation" small metal plaque, appears to have formerly been attached to something but is now separate (Box 68)
  - Time Magazine Cover (copy), 2000; Edward Bleier and Martin Pompadur (Oversize 1)
  - Time Warner Entertainment Company, L.P. plaque, "$600,000,000 Motion Picture and Television Series Syndication Securitization" (Box 68)
  - TV Land 'TV Set' clock (Box 69)
  - Warner Brothers Studios rededication "Celebration of Tradition" souvenir WB water-tower, item is broken into two pieces, water tank and base (Box 68)
- Miscellaneous
  - Broadcasting and Cable Magazine, 1994; Story on Bleier (Oversize 1)
  - Bugs Bunny 50th Birthday Brochure, 1989 (Oversize 1)
  - Bugs Bunny and Ed Bleier promotional photo contact sheet (Oversize 1)
  - Bugs Bunny Hollywood Reporter ad, 1987 (Oversize 1)
  - Bugs Bunny Variety Ad, 1989 (Oversize 1)
  - Digital TV Study, 8 Feb 1996 (Box 70)
  - Looney Tunes character postcards, color, 9 copies (Oversize 1)
  - Looney Tunes Magazine, 1990 (Oversize 1)
  - Nickelodeon story boards (Oversize 1)
  - Promo drawings for Quackbusters, on tracing paper, large scale (Oversize 1)
  - "Trade Barriers to Exports of U.S. Filmed Entertainment", 2003; 2005; 2 volumes (Box 70)
  - United Nations World Television Forum, November 1996 (Box 70)
  - Variety Article on video tastes, 1968 (Oversize 1)
  - Warner Brothers character color ad, Cablevision Magazine, 1994 (Oversize 1)
- Printed material
  - Network TV Program Reports, 1971-1989 (Box 71)
  - Cable TV Guides, 1988-1989 (Box 71)
  - Newspaper articles on new fall seasons, 1987-1993 (Box 71)
  - Network TV Program Development, 1976-1984 (Box 71)
  - Network TV Program Development, 1984-1991 (Box 72)
  - Variety Program Book, Fall 1992 (Box 72)
  - Cable TV Materials
    - Facts (Box 72)
    - Lineups (Box 72)
    - Station Listings (Box 72)
    - Pay-Per-View Development (Box 72)
    - 1979 Arbitron ADI Map (Box 72)
    - Investment Research (Box 73)
  - Awards, Parties, Programs
    See also Memorabilia, boxes 68 and 69, for plaques and souvenirs.
    - Center for Communication Luncheon, 1998; 2000,; 2001,; 2003; 2 folders (Box 73)
    - Center for Communication Flyer (Box 73)
    - Council on Foreign Relations
      - Annual report, 2006 (Box 73)
      - Pacific trip material, 2007; background reading, participant bios; 2 volumes (Box 101)
    - Encore! Concert, 1994 (Box 73)
    - Guild Hall, 1998-2000; 2002-2004; programs; 6 folders (Box 73)
    - Juvenile Diabetes Foundation (Box 73)
    - Livent Inc. Annual Report (Box 73)
    - MT & R Roster (Box 73)
    - Time View, World View address (Box 73)
    - UJA luncheon speech (Box 73)
  - Aspen Institute: The Social Impact of TV (Box 73)
  - Paine Webber Conference on the Media Outlook (Box 73)
  - IRTS 12th Annual Seminar (Box 73)
  - Broadcasting and Cable (Box 73)
  - Communications and Society Program, 2 folders (Box 74)
  - The End of TV: Future Industry Perspective (Box 74)
  - Movies of the Future (Box 74)
  - Smithsonian, 1981 (Box 74)
  - Avenue (Box 74)
  - WB Documents: Classic Thrillers (Box 74)
  - The MGM Family Network (Box 74)
  - WB Internal: TV Distribution (Box 74)
  - WB Film Gallery, 1973 (Box 74)
  - WB Golden Anniversary Book (Box 74)
  - WB Movies Packet Vol. 16 (Box 75)
  - WB TV Movie Distribution Volumes 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 5 volumes (Box 75)
  - WB Series Catalog, Spring 2000 (Box 75)
  - WB New Media Packet (Box 75)
  - Time Warner Management Directory, 1991 (Box 76)
  - Time Warner Telephone Directory, 1998 (Box 76)
  - Africa: A Joint Communications Effort Between ABC and 3M Promotions Package (Box 77)
- Project files
  - Early PPV/Home Video Dev.
    - MCA DiscoVision, 1978 (Box 78)
    - TV Cable Week, 1983 (Box 78)
    - ABC Tele1st, 1984 (Box 78)
    - Time Warner NYC Cable '91 Quantum Interactive, 1991 (Box 78)
    - Time Warner NYC Cable '91, 1991 (Box 78)
    - Time Warner Cable Orlando Spectrum (Box 78)
  - On Demand Article on Hit-Movie VOD (Box 78)
  - Home Video Industry Outlook (Box 78)
  - GE Consulting (Box 78)
  - "1776" Sponsored Exhibition Proposal (Box 78)
  - WB Domestic Pay-TV Cable and Network Features (Box 78)
  - Quincy Jones: The Dude/Bugs Bunny, 2 folders (Box 78)
  - WB Presents Bugs Bunny in Concert (Box 78)
  - Animation Deals (Box 78)
  - Broadcast Standards: The Matrix (Box 78)
  - Network Movie Sales DGA Editing Notices (Box 78)
  - Animation ratings (Box 79)
  - Movie ratings (Box 79)
  - Total network sales (Box 79)
  - Aspen Institute: Communication Leaders (Box 79)
  - SFM Holiday Network
    - General (Box 79)
    - Yes, Virginia (Box 79)
    - Yes, Virginia/Heidi (Box 79)
    - Treasure Island (Box 79)
    - Spirit of St. Louis (Box 79)
  - Chuck Jones
    - Working Documents, 2 folders (Box 79)
    - Project File: BB/RR Contracts, 1978 (Box 79)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 79)
    - Chuck Amuck (Box 79)
    - Chuck Jones '92 (Box 79)
    - Chuck Jones (Box 80)
    - Bugs Bunny, Chuck Jones (Box 80)
  - Bugs Bunny Sat. AM, 1991-1995; 3 folders (Box 80)
  - ABC Bugs Bunny Sat. AM, 1998-1990 (Box 80)
  - ABC: BB/RR Show, 1986-1987; correspondence (Box 80)
  - ABC: BB/RR Show, 1986-1987; correspondence; 2 folders (Box 81)
  - ABC: BB/RR Show, 1984-1985; 2 folders (Box 81)
  - CBS: BB/DD Primetime, 1989-1995; 2 folders (Box 81)
  - BB/DD Specials, 1986-1988; 2 folders (Box 81)
  - CBS: BB/RR Show, 1982-1985 (Box 81)
  - CBS: BB/RR Show, 1982-1985; 2 folders (Box 82)
  - Looney Tunes Promo Poster (Box 82)
  - CBS: Bugs Bunny Primetime (Box 82)
  - Bugs Bunny Prime Time Specials, thru 1981 (Box 82)
  - BB/RR Show Sat AM, thru 1981 (Box 82)
  - CBS: BB/RR Agreements, thru 1981 (Box 82)
  - CBS: BB Negotiations, 1981 (Box 82)
  - BB/RR Contract, 1975-1977 (Box 82)
  - Daffy Duck, thru 1984; 2 folders (Box 82)
  - Jeff Bergman / Looney Tunes voices (Box 82)
  - Greg Ford (Box 83)
  - Hareport, 2 folders (Box 83)
  - NBC/DD Negotiations, 1981 (Box 83)
  - Film Treatment: Car Toons! (Box 83)
  - Film Treatment: Sam the Interpol Eagle (Box 83)
  - Film Treatment: The Year the Eagle Quit (Box 83)
  - Film Script: KidVid! (Box 83)
  - Mel Blanc/Noel Blanc (Box 83)
  - Mel Blanc (Box 83)
  - Mel Blanc (Box 84)
  - Mel Blanc, Bugs Bunny Learning Center (Box 84)
  - ABC Family Fun Fair Mall Tour, 2 folders (Box 84)
  - WB Cartoons / Atari, 1986 (Box 84)
  - The Mel Blanc Roast (Box 84)
  - Film Treatment: Sam the Interpol Eagle (Box 84)
  - Film Treatment: CarToons! (Box 84)
  - Hal Geer (Box 84)
  - Friz Freleng, 2 folders (Box 84)
  - Articles on TV, 1977-1984; 3 folders (Box 84)
  - Articles (policy, books, etc), 1978-1990; 3 folders (Box 85)
  - Network Feature Production & Sales, 2000-2001; 2 folders (Box 85)
  - Network Sales Summaries, pre-1976 thru 1984 (Box 86)
  - Interview for Wall Street Journal re: Ted Turner, transcript (Box 86)
  - Working papers
    - 1995-1997 (Box 85)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 86)
    - 1996-1997, 3 folders (Box 86)
    - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 86)
    - 1999-2004, personal (Box 87)
    - 2000, Retirement, 5 Year Plan, Video-on-Demand Planning (Box 87)
    - 2000, Turner Conflicts, Revenue Breakout Animation (Box 87)
    - 2000, Video-on-Demand Negotiations (Box 87)
    - 2002-2007, EB Concept for Cable News Networks (Box 87)
    - 2002-2007, "Breakthrough Concept for Cable News Networks" (Box 87)
  - Ed Bleier TW Digital Planning, 1999 (Box 87)
  - Creation of Home Video VCRs and Discs (Box 87)
  - Creation of Home Video VCRs and Discs, 3 folders (Box 88)
  - Rockefeller Center / Radio City Music Hall (Box 88)
  - Radio City Music Hall Facility Guide (Box 88)
  - New York Cosmos Revival, 2 folders (Box 88)
  - Pre-1948 WB Cartoons Sold to PRM (Box 89)
  - Radio City Services (Box 89)
  - To the End of Time (Box 89)
  - EB Speeches (Box 89)
  - Pay TV (Box 89)
  - MPA Market Statistics, 2005 (Box 89)
  - Active Sales (Box 89)
  - Ed Bleier Memoir Draft (Box 89)
  - WB Philosophy / Sales PowerPoint (Box 89)
  - U.S. Research: Television Broadcasting Industry (Box 89)
  - Seminar: The Pay Per View Future, 1988; cassette tapes and booklet (Box 90)
  - Seminar: The Pay Per View Future, 1990; cassette tapes and booklet (Box 90)
  - Aspen Institute: The Future of Commercial Television, 1965-1975 (Box 90)
  - Communications and Society Programs, The Aspen Institute (Box 90)
  - Ed's Personal Notebook (Box 90)
  - Tradoc: U.S. Army Tour (Box 90)
  - Theatrical Billings (Box 91)
  - Pre-1948 WB Features / VA Deal (Box 91)
  - Speeches, misc (Box 91)
  - Wall Street Journal Articles on a 4th Network (Box 91)
  - Film Treatment: One Christmas in Boothville (Box 91)
  - Film Treatment: The Penny Pinchers (Box 91)
  - Newall & Yohe, Inc Film Outlines (Box 91)
- Thanksgiving Ceremony files
  - Recipes, 4 folders (Box 92)
  - Promotional/Editorial Plans, 2 folders (Box 92)
  - Book drafts (Box 92)
  - Research (Box 92)
  - Drafts / research (Box 93)
  - Plymouth research (Box 93)
  - Project proposal / timeline (Box 93)
  - History, draft (Box 93)
  - Thanksgiving Ceremony (research) (Box 93)
  - Extending the Thanksgiving Spirit (Box 93)
  - Manuscript (Box 93)
  - After-Dinner drafts (Box 93)
  - Thanksgiving, old (Box 93)
  - Draft (Box 93)
  - Thanksgiving Ceremony drafts, 2 folders (Box 94)
  - Website (Box 94)
  - After-Dinner Festivities (Box 94)
  - Poetry (Box 94)
  - Thanksgiving Books: resources, 2 folders (Box 94)
  - History section (Box 94)
  - History section research, 2 folders (Box 94)
  - Graphics outtakes, 2 folders (Box 95)
  - Political speeches / proclamations (Box 95)
  - Hymns, psalms and poems, 2 folders (Box 95)
  - Book draft, 3 folders (Box 95)
  - Research, 2 folders (Box 96)
  - Book research, 2 folders (Box 96)
  - Sales agreements, 2 folders (Box 96)
  - Booklet drafts (Box 96)
  - Book drafts, 2 folders (Box 97)
  - Book chapter drafts, 2 folders (Box 97)
  - Full book draft, 2 folders (Box 97)
  - Invoices (Box 97)
  - Books (Box 97)
  - Permissions file (Box 98)
  - Magazines (Box 98)
  - Book deal (Box 98)
  - Agreements (Box 98)
  - Correspondence, 7 folders (Box 99)
  - Book Agreements (Box 99)
  - Proposals and book launch (Box 100)
  - Party lists, reviews, etc, 2 folders (Box 100)
  - Reviews, etc, 2 folders (Box 100)
  - Book Release Party, 2003; 2 folders (Box 100)